[Music playing]
Somewhere in time and space, Mike Nelson and his robot pals
are caught in an endless chase.
Pursued by a woman whose name is Pearl,
an evil gal who wants to rule the world.
She threw a few things in her purse.
And in her rocket ship, she hunts
him all across the universe.
I'll get you.
I'll send him cheesy movies.
The worst I can find.
He'll have to sit and watch them all.
And I'll monitor his mind.
Now keep in mind Mike can't control
where the movies begin or end.
He'll try to keep his sanity with the help
of his robot friends.
Robot rules called Kebab.
You're on.
Jigsaw.
Tom Servo.
Check me out.
I am Ripley.
If you're wondering how he eats and breathes
and other science facts, just repeat to yourself,
it's just a show.
You should really just relax.
Called Mystery Science Theater 3000.
[Roaring]
[Clattering]
[Beeping]
Freeze on the satellite of love.
This BP is dropping fast.
We're losing him.
The hell we are.
Clear.
Come on.
Come on now.
Live.
Come on.
More broccoli?
It isn't broccoli I want.
It's you.
Mm.
Look at me.
You know what I think?
I think you knew that chicken poppa was stuck with explosives,
didn't you?
Didn't you?
No.
Come on, answer the question, you scowl.
Ah, stop lying.
Oh, crow.
Come on.
Come on, you're going to make it, buddy.
No.
The sauce, it's too rich.
It's too thick.
Oh, no.
Save yourself.
Crow, take my hand.
Don't make me shoot you.
Crow.
And now, tonight's episode.
You'll pay, Nelson.
You'll pay with your miserable life.
Tom, we're back in the regular world now.
How could you sleep with Amanda?
What?
Oh, oh.
I'm going to check what's going on in the castle now.
Ah, sure, great.
Fine.
Can you stop choking me?
Let me hang on.
I can't.
I mean, a hot dog, sure.
A hot dog is one thing.
But to then place chili inside the hot dog, a puddle of chili.
Indeed, it is.
I mean, where do they come up with ingenious things like this?
That stuff is way beyond you and me, my friend.
I think so.
Well, I'm going to go make us another batch.
Good idea.
No, hurry back, Bobo, there's a great fight on Jerry Springer.
Observer.
Well, it's all too clear, isn't it?
We've been knocking ourselves out, reconstituting our exploded planet,
searching the entire universe for you, Observer,
and then to find you here like this.
Living like some gross, smelly animal thing.
Oh, Observer.
But I didn't even know you were still alive.
I mean, I'm still all powerful and omniscient and know all things,
but how was I to know, really?
I made more chili dogs.
Would you like one?
Who are you?
Oh, I know who you are.
You're those really white other guys who have their brains in pans, too,
only you're the mean ones.
I'm going to tell not to...
Not to that.
Well, Observer, it certainly would be nice to have you with us
as we once again made our civilization the grandest in the cosmos,
but are you really even Observer anymore?
Observer.
I still have my powers, if that's what you mean.
I mean, watch, watch, watch.
Do you remember that brute who blew up our planet?
I will blight him with something so horrible that you just watch this.
[music]
[gasps]
Oh.
Oh, hey, thank you, brain guy.
Oh, it's quite nice, actually.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Oh, see, nobody wants to get a tie.
Don't you see what a terrible gift that is?
I'll tell you what, I'll try again.
Two out of three.
Oh, you're a pathetic sop.
It will take you with us and blow this place up.
Come on, dummy.
Well.
So, brain guy, you're planning to leave us.
Yes, just the right civilization that needs me.
We are not good enough for you, I understand.
Nothing personal, really.
No, it's fine.
No, it's nothing against you.
No, it's just that I don't need my help blowing up the world and everything.
Fine.
I'll tell you what, I'll send you one last movie to Mike.
Mike, your movie this week is called The Deadly Bees.
See, it's just that my civilization needs me and so I have to--
No, no, that's fine.
Oh, don't leave, brain guy.
I love you.
[sobbing]
That's a pet.
Wow, already you've spilled about a gallon of gravy on your tie.
I mean, how clumsy are you, Mike?
You didn't even get the gravy.
Oh, the movie's fine.
Oh, hey, I can give this movie 28 stars.
[chuckles]
Actually, we're not that busy.
We go at a fairly relaxed pace.
Christopher Robin decided on a diabolical plan to kill Pooh.
Man, that guy needs to change his furnace filter more often.
Okay.
Friendly Swear Words Productions.
Hi, I'm in the movie.
See, that's me right there.
I'm in the movie.
How about you?
Now, please, according to physicists, we can't fly.
Have they named every bee?
This is gonna take forever.
Sure, I'm a little clumsy, but I wouldn't say I'm a bumblebee.
Well, that's the Hee Haw Fond.
How can it be dead?
[music]
I don't wanna be a worker bee.
I wanna be a middle management bee.
Now, gang, that queen just doesn't do anything for me.
She's not my titan, sorry.
Good job, son.
Heck, always should have a king bee.
Why not?
Down with the matriarchy.
There's a bug bomb in the hive,
so they gotta stay out for a couple hours.
Every single bee had to sign on with Sam.
Squishing up a baby, human being.
See, how do you like it?
It's pretty funny, huh?
Lilacs, we have lilacs.
This is not a drill.
Hey, special effects by Michael Collins,
so everything gets blown up then.
[music]
Oh, yeah, the birds, huh?
Not B-Y-R birds, but still, they're birds.
[music]
A taste for honey,
the novel on which this movie was beyazed.
I'm wearing a rugby shirt.
[music]
Here at the giant headquarters of the bee corporation.
I suppose you'll want Christmas off, Cratchit.
Mostly routine stuff, as usual.
Why on earth does this one come to the ministry?
I have your knickers.
Quite an interesting one, though.
Fellow reckons he developed a strain of killer bees.
Fantastic.
Oh, not him again.
Chapped on Seagull Island, isn't it?
That's right.
Have you heard from him before, then?
Heard from him?
I was married to him.
Well, we must have filled about half a dozen waste paper baskets
with bums from him over the years.
Not as a fruitcake he is.
Aren't they bees?
Well, he says unless you take him seriously this time,
he's going to prove his point once and for all
and unleash his bees to kill someone.
Well, don't think he means it, do you?
Well, yeah.
[music]
Eight miles wrong.
There's me, blanking me, too.
We got an understanding all right.
They can only allow the shame.
Guys, just skip the music and go right to the heroin.
It means that you love me, I love you.
And nobody else would you.
Don't let your mom dress the band.
Cause I saw that I loved you before.
G-G-G-F-G, out.
That's all that I need you for.
That's all that I love you for.
Oh, that's all that I need you for.
Audiences limited by those health pamphlets.
I said that's all that I need you for.
Yes, well, there's these for you to sign for the studio
and three or four for the kids outside.
Oh, Vicki, for goodness sake, what's the matter with you?
I'm so tired.
And hot for some reason.
Exhausted.
Sweetie, come on now, it's not...
But I just got back from the Antarctic.
There's only one number.
Then you can have a nice rest in the car on the way to the theater.
Two shows and then home to bed.
And I'll switch the phone off until tomorrow morning.
The Skinnies.
Thank you, the birds.
I'm sure we all wish them the very best on their forthcoming tour of America.
Should they ever get one?
Now kids, here she is.
This week's guest star, the very lovely Vicki Robin.
I think.
Recorded in rich monorail sound.
She's in the shower.
A bear!
What is that?
I can't sing, it's too hot.
My baby took me to a dance last night.
It was a pretty good time, I guess.
And when we danced, he held me oh so tight.
Then I left his side a minute, maybe two.
When I returned, he was with somebody new.
The female Anthony Newley.
Stop the music.
Well that's good advice.
He's dancing with another girl.
The poor woman, right?
Stop that music.
He's got my heart in a whirl.
He's a perfumeless girlfriend.
He would have waited just another minute more.
Before he stepped with someone else out on the floor.
She's coming after us, back up.
I've got to change the storm windows.
Arrival show is made.
Stop the music, I love him care.
Stop the music, I love him can't you see.
Whoa, Sonny Liston came in and hit her.
Songwriter chatter.
Stop the music.
He still lip syncs better than Jewel.
He has got my heart in a whirl.
Man, long songs are going to take forever.
Stop the music.
That came early Nelson, let's go.
Three weeks doctor.
What a blimey rotter.
Do you know what that could mean to us?
I know what it means to Miss Robbins.
Lord Melbury.
Hey, I'm afraid as a manager you'll just have to suffer your 10% of the pain.
Well of course Dr. Vicki's health is all that really matters but.
Good.
Then you'll have no objection if I take the law into my own hands and arrange a convalescent right away.
Why where are you sending her?
I have an old friend who has a farm on Seagull Island.
Hello.
I want to make a personal call please to a Mr. Ralph Hargrove.
Ralph, you in there? Ralph, you got a call?
Yeah, this will calm down her nerves.
Let's make sure there's enough Komodo dragons on the premises too.
Babe here, what can I do you for?
On a dare this guy built his farm blindfolded.
Mary, answer that phone.
It's not enough you're going to eat me, I have to take your messages.
I'm scared anytime mister.
Thanks for stopping to share with top choice.
Hello George, haven't heard from you for ages.
Who?
Lillian Hellman, she's fine.
Yeah, tomorrow for two weeks.
It's alright, it's out of season but if she doesn't mind taking us as she finds us.
Alright I'll make the bill tomorrow.
Yeah, see you.
Bye now.
Another Territon?
A paying guest at this time of the year, you must be out of your mind.
I love you too darling.
She's a patient of a very old friend of mine.
She's coming whether you like it or not.
I'll get a girl out from the village, give you a hand.
Yes, you like that won't you?
Has the hate gone out of our marriage?
Wow.
Hey, they're growing Bill the Cat.
Very small horse farms in England.
Yeah.
Well, stop for a length of hose, put it in the pipe, that should take care of my little problem.
I'm going to try a different home, maybe they'll let me live here.
Hello David.
Morning Mr. Bargrove.
How can I get you?
The usual.
It's 9am, why so late?
Make it a double then.
Alright, now we're in England.
Andy Capp, the movie.
What'll you have?
I'll have a half a bit, thanks very much.
You up for a crop circle later?
On the slate I suppose.
But of course.
Is Doris about?
She's in the kitchen.
Want to say something special?
Naked cricket.
I've got someone coming to stay for a couple of weeks, I'm worried if she'd give us a hand in the house.
Mrs. Hargrove, not too good then?
Not brilliant, no.
She's got her cigarettes and all.
Doris, Doris!
Coming!
My they're a joyful people.
Yes?
Mr. Hargrove wants to ask you a favour.
A depressed middle aged man, well.
It's morning and he's drinking mine.
You want something?
Would you like to come up to the farm and give us a hand in the house for a couple of weeks?
I've got a guest arriving.
I'd love to.
A little ankle, yeah.
Who's coming?
Some singer, Vicki Robbins.
Vicki Robbins?
That should make us quite a tourist attraction.
This has too much colour in it.
Hey, it's still crooked.
She's dressed for a shift at Perkins.
Have you seen Tess's meat?
Pardon?
The dog's meat, have you seen it?
No, it's in the larder I think. Would you like to go and look?
No, I'll go. She'll only take it from me anyway.
The filthiest conversation ever.
Doris, this looks marvellous.
I don't know what I would have done without you.
It's alright. I'm only too glad to help.
Suppose you've heard about the dog's meat.
Yes, well I'd better get out of me to boat.
Oh, hi boat.
Cathy Lee Gifford arrives to see the dog's meat.
Vole patrol.
It's not a licence plate. They're telling us what hymns we'll be singing.
Picked up Jeremiah Johnson.
Plachman's mustard gave me this code.
Come along.
So, how well does a crap farm do actually?
Your room through here.
In my room.
Oh, I need some air.
Hello. Who are you then? That's Tess. Hello. Hello. I'm Doris.
Oh yes. Mr Hargrove told me about you. You're the tard.
I hope you like the room. Yes, it's very nice.
Good. Oh, the bathroom. It's up here.
Bathroom? Yes, you put your business in there and then you pull the chain.
I hope you're not going to find it too dull on these islands, Robbins.
No. Why is she carrying a pinata?
I think it's going to be great.
It's a little smod in the straightened flowers.
Hey, an inflatable girl. All right.
Doris tells me you're quite a celebrity, Miss Robbins.
If it's peace and quiet you want, you've come to the right place.
No screaming teenagers here.
It's perfect. I'm beginning to feel better already.
Have some more toast, Miss Robbins.
No thank you, Mrs Hargrove. And the honey was delicious.
Why, thank you. Do you know something?
We grow our own.
What's that speciality about?
Don't encourage her, Miss Robbins.
She spends far too much time with those bees as it is, instead of running the farm.
My wife doesn't seem to realize the amount of work involved in bee farming.
Can I eat in my room?
As far as I'm concerned, it's worth every moment.
I've never tasted honey like it.
Oh, she had to bring up the honey.
Are you very fond of animals, Miss Robbins?
Yes, I am. Especially dogs.
Oh, excuse me. I've moved.
I have a pleasant day, Miss Robbins. Why don't you go for a walk or something?
Yes, I'd like that. May I take her with me?
Yes, of course. She'd love a walk.
She certainly seems to have taken to you.
Hello?
She never leaves me as a rule.
Oh, Miss Robbins, telephone.
Oh, that's probably my baby asking me to go to a dance last night.
Hang on, she's just coming.
Thank you.
Hello?
Now, nothing to do with work, baby.
Surprised, huh?
I'm just calling to see that you've arrived safely.
Yes, I'm fine.
Good.
Sure, it's great here.
Good, that's it. You have a nice rest.
Yeah. Bye.
Why didn't I marry a cigarette?
I have friends and stuff, do you?
That was my agent. He worries about me all the time.
Come on, Tess.
Bye, Mrs. Hargrove.
Oh, by the way, where are the hives? I'd love to have a look at them on the way out.
He doesn't like people around the hives. He says it disturbs the bees.
In that case, I'll keep out of their way.
I was hoping to ride a bee later, but I guess not.
Come on, Tess.
My agent is nicotine.
Here, catch it.
Good girl.
Oh, does it have to be that stick? Any stick do?
Come on, girl.
She's got a great arm.
You're a new teacher, aren't you?
Tess!
That cat owes me half a rabbit carcass.
Come on, out you go.
Mmm, delicious cat. Thank you.
Hello! You're Miss Robbins, aren't you?
Hello. I hope Tess hasn't done any damage.
Oh, I shouldn't think so.
Come in. Come along in. We'll have a look.
I used to live next to the Jeffersons.
You stay there, Tess.
I heard you were staying at the Hargroves.
My name is Manfred.
You've heard of my earth band?
Oh, come along here.
Mmm.
Well, they don't seem to have broken anything.
What a beautiful room.
Did you paint it with your own blood?
Look at these butterflies.
Did you catch them yourself?
Yes, I did. It's one of my homies.
Here with that and my bees.
Oh, you keep bees too?
Yes.
I didn't see any hives.
No, you wouldn't. I haven't got any, it sounds.
You're dead, bird. You're mine.
Oh, don't you doubt it.
Look, I'll show you.
It's decorated like a bad Chinese restaurant in there.
I had my ape fury built here so that I can keep an eye on them.
See, they don't get up to any mischief.
Fascinating, aren't they?
Well, that one is, but the others are boring.
My ape fury never gets to the ships.
Okay.
Would you like a cup of tea?
No, thank you. I had an enormous breakfast before I left the farm.
Good.
How were they looking after you at the Hargroves?
Oh, very well, thank you.
Splendid.
But I must say we're all delighted to have you on the island.
I hope you're enjoying your stay with us.
Look, if you're not too busy sometime,
perhaps you'd like to come over and have tea with me,
sample some of my delicious honey.
It's much better than Hargroves, but don't tell him I said so.
I'd love that.
Hey, an empty ashtray. What gives here?
Our vacation's really kicking in now.
Love that Seagull Island.
If you would only give me half a chance
to show you how I love you, baby, let me love you, baby.
Sorry, my tympanic membrane's at burst.
Can I help you?
No, no. I was wondering if I could borrow this book.
I was looking at Mr. Manpitt's bees this afternoon.
I got quite interested.
I realize you don't know much about life here on the island,
but may I suggest you take my advice
and don't repeat your visit...
Comma.
To Mr. Manfred.
Period.
It's dangerous to involve yourself in matters you don't understand.
What would I ever do then?
Like what?
Like, uh...
A rock.
Bees, Miss Robbins.
Bees?
Turn off the light when you're finished, will you?
Yes, sir.
Hello, Mike.
Oh, hi, Crow.
Nice panaloon.
Oh, never mind that.
I'm smitten with love for the fair lady Hargrove.
Who?
From the movie? You mean the cigarette hag?
Don't call her that.
Sorry. Go on with your story.
Thank you.
I've written a sonnet in her honor, classic English form, 14 lines, iambic feet.
Great. Uh, what's with Curly here?
Oh, me?
I'm just sitting in on crumhorn.
Okay, well, rockin'. Let's hear it.
Okay.
Hit it.
As England's rotting springtime begs to loom,
I spy thee, sitting, smoking with thy dog.
I long to fill my lungs with your perfume,
apt several samplings of the local grog.
Effluvia!
I would rather die than switch
to gaily dance my claws through smokey locks
is my delight, though some would call you bi-
ah, which I love thee, filter, flavor, pack, or box.
I flit, for springtime happens every you,
and fly to spy thy scowl in barnyard fair.
Sweet pan's delight, I kiss a mole or two
as satisfying flavor fills the air.
With loved black lungs will from the heavens choke
a silly millimeter longer of love's smoke.
Thank you.
Okay.
I gotta go brush my teeth. See ya.
Wait, I have a canto as well.
Ah, forget it.
We'll be right back.
Bright tonight. Don't wanna get burned out there.
That's what I would have seen had I been in there.
Don't walk into the psych.
Catherine, is it- oh, it's you.
I'll take this watch. You sleep.
[screeching]
Ew, icky barn sounds.
Oh, and this starts the great Chicago flood.
I'm temporarily not perky.
What a pain.
Those windows should get the lead out.
Easy, Mike. Don't hit.
Good morning, you.
Can someone help me down from up here?
Ugh. I don't know.
I think my body's rejecting this movie, isn't it?
Ha! House dress action.
[sigh]
Okay, Sarah. Sarah.
Hosanna, superstar. Hosanna, superstar.
Hosanna, superstar.
Still not enough for Robert Downey Jr.
Pop star afraid of a needle?
Gee.
He takes his pudding intravenously.
Oh, I am so relaxed right now. This vacation is doing me wonders.
Can't believe all this blood came out of that one turnip.
It's our lovemaking night.
So you're back.
I thought I'd married a farmer, not a vet, up at all hours of the night.
I wasn't aware that I was disturbing him.
Anyway, I have some rather important work I've got to do.
Work? It's a great pity you couldn't manage a little of that during the day around the farm.
My farm.
Old McWartface had a farm.
See, baby?
She'd be a little more relaxed at the Lockhorns.
Now?
Now you're on my leg.
She's grinding her teeth down.
Hello.
What time is it?
Nine o'clock.
It's a gorgeous day.
Did you sleep well?
Like a top. Once I'd got to sleep.
I don't care.
Doris? Yes?
Do I look like Lee Marvin?
Nothing.
A bucket of filth, filth, filth, a bucket of filth.
Man, Pig, what'd you do in that bucket?
Don't give me that look. Just clean my bucket.
Red Horse also plays Wilson on home improvement.
Go to hell, world.
That looks a lot better.
Okay, jump at him. Go.
Chickens must all be scared Ozzy Osbourne's going to show up later.
Thanks for covering your hand in delicious beef tallow.
You stay there, Tess.
Look at that horse's ass.
I admit, I picked that horse.
Well, I'll just walk around and look hopeful. That should help.
What are you doing in here?
Just looking around. Do you mind?
No. I have to kill you now.
Well, I shouldn't have thought there was much to interest you in a stable.
I do a lot of riding.
I'm fond of horses.
How are you?
Well, if you thought you were going to get some riding here, I'm afraid you're out of luck. The man is sick.
So what am I paying for again?
The vet told me to keep her stabled and very quiet. So, if you don't mind.
Take your kettle drum and your screaming and get out of here. Go on.
There's that towel I've been looking for.
The ducks are sick too. Forget it.
I don't see any meat in the towel, man.
Get out of here!
Hey, none of those ducks have seen it all.
Damn, I had to get up.
Do you mind if I use your phone? I thought I'd ring my agent.
Well, I just tried to use it myself. It's out of order again.
Does that often happen?
Yes, I'm afraid it does.
Anyway, I was going to take a walk. I expect Mr. Manfred's got a phone.
No idea, I'm sure.
We don't see much of Mr. Manfred. My husband doesn't like it.
Would you like a glass of cigarettes?
Thank you.
Turn down that annoying Beatles group again.
I've checked that number again on Seagull Island. It's still out of order.
We'll see if there's another phone on the island where they'll take a message.
If we don't get her back here for the recording on Tuesday, we won't have a number in the charts for Christmas.
I'm too busy drinking to call.
Get me directory inquiries, please.
After all I've done for that girl.
And she's off enjoying herself at a time like this.
It must have been about two o'clock when everything seemed to happen.
What do you mean?
Well, noises from the stable and people wandering around in the yard.
I don't mind telling you I soon locked the door and hid under the bedclothes.
You sure you didn't dream all this?
Well, I thought I might have done it first.
When this morning I went into the stable and saw these terrible hypodermic punches all over that wretched horse.
Yes, the horse is on the horse.
Don't say that.
You're very observant, aren't you?
Did you say something?
No, sir, sir, please quit trying to milk us.
Yeah, why do people even try living anyway?
Well, that should be my life haters club calling.
Mary!
Joe Orton and his roommate got along better than these two.
I was out in the barn. I thought I'd come in and tell you how much I love you.
Hello?
No, you're right, girlfriend. He doesn't understand you.
It's a tobacco growers council calling to thank you.
Stop feeding that animal for just one minute.
No, I can't.
He's the only friend I've got around this place.
Sure, they argue, but the sex is great.
Well, thank you for the coffee.
Oh, you're very welcome.
The bees made it, you know.
Now, you're not to worry.
Okay.
All right?
Goodbye.
Bye-bye.
All right? Okay. Goodbye. All right?
Fly away, Raisinettes. Fly away.
There's got to be a hand with gravy on it somewhere.
Tramp Douglas, super spy.
Chances are it won't kill me, so down it goes.
And Field Marshal Montgomery arrives.
Going down to the pub. Do you want to come?
Oh, well...
Come on, we'll do it good.
All right.
Yes, the pub. Plenty of warm beer, boiled meat, and old guys.
Very aggressive leaves.
Well, it's about that time, Tree.
Come on, guys. We're supposed to be deadly. We haven't done squat.
What's that, boy?
Use a front projection system or a beam splitter and you'll get better results with your process shots?
Do you bees have meat on your hands?
She's reading Bitter Wife Weekly.
Are pigs in trouble?
She hasn't moved that fast since Lucky Strikes went on sale.
I'm racing out to sleep with your husband.
Tess.
Tess!
Aw, a bathroom rug.
Appeal to your audience. Kill the cute dog.
Oh, if only I hadn't quit smoking. Oh, wait, I didn't. Oh, good.
He did this.
He did it.
Fog horn, leg horn did it.
Him and his horrible bees.
Just for that I'll redouble my smoking and withhold more sex.
Can I get a pain, please?
All right, drunk, let's go faster.
Walks like Kevin McHale.
This will really light my cigarettes.
What are you doing? You must be magic.
Take me along.
Wow, look at her go. I didn't realize cigarettes had so many cigarettes.
I'm going to get you.
Wow, look at her go. I didn't realize cigarettes had so many vitamins.
It's Popeye in drag.
Okay, okay, okay.
What do you think you're doing?
Leave me alone.
They killed the dog. They killed Tess.
What's the matter with you?
You run out of your mind.
I don't want to run out of my mind.
For God's sake.
Well, I knew when I married her she was a spirit of little Billy.
Help me carry the queen, you guys. She's very heavy.
Save the royal jelly.
Bee draft.
You at least have shuffleboard here.
Valerie Bertinelli in the outlaw.
Bee's had too many extension plugs in one outlet.
Yep.
She's afraid the nine gallons of hairspray on her head will go up.
I used my last match.
Boy, I don't know why they didn't include this scene in "That's Entertainment."
Yeah.
Wow.
Well, I suspect awesome.
I made medallions of dogs.
What time do you want lunch, Mrs. Hargrove?
Whatever time he gets back from that pub of yours.
When will that be?
Well, didn't he tell you?
He's in Starfleet.
Fun.
Romulan ale for you?
One of Elizabeth Kubler-Ross' stages of grief. Heavy smoking.
I wish they'd let me eat indoors.
There. I finished my chore. I'm done.
One last scoop to scoop up.
Do you want to go torch an ant colony later?
Good night, Mrs. Hargrove.
Starring John Hurt as Mrs. Hargrove.
Bees live in a sushi tray.
The true story of the sex and murder behind the making of your breakfast honey.
Ah, it's her walk-in cigarette humidor.
But getting a bar now absolutely bizarre.
Maybe the horse will eat meat from my hand.
Yeah, she seems depressing now when you're in the office.
I'm not sure.
I'm just a little bit worried about her.
Yeah, she seems depressing now, but you should see her when she starts playing her banjo.
This is nothing that a little Centrum Silver wouldn't take care of.
Did El Greco do the backdrops?
To think that she was once Miss East Puddingshire.
Our astronaut to stop by during dinner.
The horse has its own coffee grinder.
By the way, if you want to put me out to stud, I'll be fine with you.
Will you be my lap horse? Sit by my chair by the fire.
It's not even a sweater. It's just smoke that's clogged to her.
The bees are trying to pirate cable.
Call me a bunch of death.
Don't try calling anybody. We cut the phone lines.
The bees are setting plastic flies on her.
Ooh.
Oh.
Little present from the queen.
Everybody do your part, men. You each can't kill the whole woman.
Harry, help me. I'm stuck again.
My butt.
Careful, men. Her skin is leathery. You may lose your butt.
E-side, Deneric side.
Well, the first lockdown in her long career.
Immediately all these bees are addicted to smoking.
Buffet is open, men.
Very nice.
Watch this. I'm going to go right through the leaves.
Oh, thank you, movie. Thanks.
Well, someday I'll come home and she'll be dead finally in the...
Hey, look. All right.
Oh, no. A few of my bees are dead.
Something's smothering me.
Oh, that's my own hands.
Down, down, you rebel. Down.
Hey, what's wrong, Tom?
Oh, nothing.
It's a whole raisin killer bees thing got me going on my own venture here,
raising wood ticks for a living.
But now they're hungry and I don't know what to feed them.
Hey, Mike, have you seen my lice farm?
Oh, never mind about that. There's something doing down on Earth.
Let's see.
[sigh]
I am leaving with my bodies, no more snally-dum gorillas,
no more yelling shrewish women.
I must go.
I'm departing with my kinsmen to the planet where I come from,
even if it means destroying all I know.
Please stay, we are your friends,
though our brains are not in plans.
Please stay.
I'll give you juice if you'll only take our hand,
or take my paw.
Can you give me any reason why I shouldn't up and leave you
and blast your silly planet when I go?
There are several million reasons.
No, there's not that I can think of.
Here we go.
Okay, well, there's me.
And we've got string.
And tortillas stuffed with ham.
If you stay, I'll hold your sheets.
If you just stay, where you'll nap.
All these reasons you have given me
have totally convinced me
I really can't be going. I must stay.
There are reasons you have given me.
There are several million reasons.
Please stop and give them hell.
If you just stay, I'll hold your sheets.
I will stay.
I will hold your sheets.
If you just stay, I'll hold your sheets.
The male bird is singing to his mate.
You can just see his throat moving.
Now, the female bird can hear that song, fortunately.
But the human ear cannot.
Most human ears, it is.
But how can a bird...
Oh, no, no, not a bird. A mob.
A death's head mob.
Now, this is one.
They get their name because of the death's head.
Now, these moths, it's quite incredible.
They can make a very high-pitched note,
which hypnotises the bees.
Why is the bees so hypnotised?
The moths invade the hive and steal the honey.
Cool.
But that still doesn't explain why you didn't get killed.
Yes, well, that was a matter of luck.
I just happened to be working on my apiary
and I had my gloves and vane
and I was able to drive them off.
The second time, I was ready for them.
I had made a recording of a note
that was of the very same frequency as that made by the moth.
Just audible to the human ear.
I was enabled to hypnotise these deadly killer bees
just long enough to capture one or two of them.
Three.
No, four. Five.
I killed three.
Look, I'll demonstrate with my own bees.
Now, why isn't a guy like this married?
Hey, hardly seems time for a Mariah Carey tape.
Since the last time, the bees have discovered tiny cotton earplugs.
No, it's all right.
As long as they can hear the note, they won't come out.
Thank you, movie.
Why should Hargrove, or whoever it was,
want to destroy your bees?
Well, he didn't want to destroy my bees.
I think he wanted to destroy them.
He wanted to destroy me.
But if that's true, all you have to do is go to the police.
Oh, I just laugh at you.
What proof do I have?
A few dead bees.
Starring Tom Cruise.
Oh, no.
Now, somewhere at the Hargrove farm,
there must be some proof.
He must keep some record of what he's doing.
I just wonder where he keeps it.
Let me stupidly get involved.
Well, he did seem very annoyed
when I went near his desk the other day.
Did he?
Well, perhaps that's where he keeps it.
I don't suppose you could...
Be naked.
Mr. Manfred, so far we have no proof of these accusations.
I can't get myself involved.
I'm on vacation.
Why don't we just wait and see what happens at the inquest?
Miss Robbins, you've been staying at the Hargrove farm
for the last week or two, have you not?
Hello.
Yes.
Why?
My doctor recommended it.
He knows Mr. Hargrove.
I see.
Miss Robbins, can you tell this inquiry anything
that might help it decide the circumstances
that led to Mrs. Hargrove's death?
The British commission.
No.
Did you notice anything unusual that day?
Were you at the farm on the day
that Mrs. Hargrove's dog was killed?
Yes.
And you still noticed nothing unusual?
No.
Ah!
Giant carp.
Wow.
Yes.
I do remember.
The dog seemed very interested
with something near the stable.
He said "woof".
And then Mr. Hargrove drove him away.
Objection.
Stupid hat.
Miss Robbins, do you know anything about bees?
No, nothing.
So you stopped after A, did you?
Thank you, Miss Robbins.
You may stand down.
Thank you.
Mr. Hargrove, would you take the chair, please?
Don't you need it for the rest of the inquest?
Oh.
Oh!
That's a good one, Gary Fryer.
Mr. Hargrove, you keep bees on your farm, do you not?
Yes.
Have you ever been stung by them?
All beekeepers receive stings from time to time.
But have you ever been stung by yours?
Often.
Psst, he's lying.
Have they ever attacked you in force
as they did your wife?
No.
Never.
Can you account for the fact
that they stung your wife to death?
No.
Hide your joy, hide your joy.
Is there anything you can tell this court
which would help it to establish
the exact cause of your wife's death?
The cause should be obvious.
She was stung to death by bees.
And her dog?
No, the dog didn't sting.
Same thing.
Why did you drive her dog away from the stable?
It was in the way.
Oh.
Can you give this court any reason
why it should not order your hides to be destroyed?
My bees were not responsible.
Whose were they?
I, uh, I'm not sure.
Mr. Hargrove.
Am I pretty?
Was your wife insured?
Yes.
And you were the only beneficiary.
You now have her farm, for instance.
Yes.
Very well, Mr. Hargrove.
You may stand down.
So, potted meat for lunch and...
Yes, pickling would be good.
You'd have to pickling all around.
Yes, pickling's good.
Well, in view of the doctor's report
and the evidence I've heard,
I have no alternative but to declare a verdict
of death by misadventure.
Whoo.
This court is closed.
She's headed to the kitchen for the last danger.
Hey, there's a weight room.
Wow, what with the great tension they've already set up.
If he caught her in there, he'd probably say,
"Don't go in there."
Yeah, that'd be great.
All right.
Wow.
Whoo.
I've got to get some pictures.
The gang will kill me if I don't get some pictures
of this beautiful place.
They've got to have soap somewhere.
[music]
Breathe deep, the gathering gloom.
Watch lights fade from every room.
His cowboy poetry.
Oh, my cursed numb hips knocked over another chair.
Okay, chair, you didn't see a thing, all right?
Here's some wood filler to keep you quiet.
James Galway's in the bathroom.
Oof.
Peter was quite worried.
He knew the wolf would be coming soon.
This is highly dangerous, but she's just got to do it
for that, well, that one guy she just met.
[music]
All right, paper, that's it.
Come on, paper, work with me.
Yeah, let me see your watermark.
Good, good, good.
Now, throw your tight face back, yes.
Stupid lawnmower, is it out of gas or...
We'll just have to artist render these papers.
She's secretly light filing things.
[music]
The movie obsessed with straightening lampshades.
Great, now I'm paranoid about pop stars sneaking around my study.
I think you are.
I was hoping to catch myself nude.
Oh, my heart stopped when she dropped those papers.
Oh.
We go now live to the heat lamp at Racks.
Yes, yes, yes.
Ah, yes, this seems to be the formula.
Excellent pictures of your thumb, thank you very much.
Just put that light on, would you?
As the movie had foreshadowed, she put the light on.
I'll just wipe the slime on my designer frock.
Now, let's have a proper look.
Does it make any sense to you?
I have a theory.
Oh, no I don't, who am I kidding?
We know that the sound of the death-said moth can hypnotize the bees.
I think Hargrove must have found, or at least must be working on some form of chemical that will mobilize the bees to attack.
Like the one you were trying to wipe off.
There was that business with the horse, wasn't there?
Yes, I think I've got it.
The rain in Spain.
Hargrove's formula.
Adrenaline. Have you ever heard of the smell of fear?
I thought that was just an expression.
A chemical.
Suddenly released into the bloodstream and carried to the surface by the sweat glands in the form of ammonia.
All animals and insects, and especially bees, are strongly attracted and sometimes aggravated by this odor.
Now if Hargrove...
Was made of ammonia.
Found some way of concentrating this smell of fear.
In my mustache.
And if he could find some way of getting it onto his...
Then he...
No person would be safe.
He could send his bees anywhere and attack anyone.
Well, let's crack open those Cheetos' paws, shall we?
Then he did kill his wife.
What can we do?
I think we better get these back before Hargrove realizes they're missing.
So, off you go. Do my dirty work.
Ah, forget sandals. This is a real vacation.
My baby sent me over to Mr. Hargrove's to wipe out his drawers last night.
Hey, he's the Hugh Hefner of Seagull Island.
There's a bobbinhead Shakespeare up there.
You know, once word gets out about this resort, it's gonna be so crowded you won't be able to get in.
Yeah.
That's how it works.
What a lovable scamp she is stealing my private papers.
It's a bee toaster.
Wow, he's got over a thousand head of bees.
Must drill myself a new mandible.
Now, this constitutes being nude in England.
Actually, this is about as titillating as a Montgomery Ward catalog.
Frankly to me, any bra is a wonder bra.
I think I'll go home and cut a hit record now.
Seems we have something you need.
We've elected you, Queen.
We're on flux.
Mind if we watch the Manchester United game in here?
Oh, what do I wear for bee weather?
My dream nose being attacked by bees in my late-form bra.
Can we use the can?
This movie objectifies bras.
I just want to get stoned before you kill me, okay?
No, she washed the towel in new fear-scented Tide.
Damn.
This is no excuse not to fight plaque.
Oh, thank you, that's very refreshing.
You know, if she really likes you, I'll be back.
You know, if she really wants to get rid of those bees, she ought to strip down and hop in the shower.
I'm not saying that out of any prurient interest, it's just good advice.
We need our best towel man in here quick.
You know, I see a red door.
Just get it to the door and turn it, men.
Now, I light my hair on fire.
Light my hair on fire.
She's going to go back to work so refreshed after this.
That's all she did.
A bee too far.
You know, with all that smoke in the air and all, it's just like when the old lady lived there.
Her plan worked perfectly.
[sniffing]
Hmm, someone's cooking towel-smoked bees.
Oh, I hope my lumpy middle-aged boyfriend is home.
Paul Prudhomme's blackening some catfish in here.
London's in the bathroom.
We brought it!
Damn.
Oh well, time to adjust lampshades.
Cameraman is hesitating.
Should I go in? I don't want to show him too much.
Ralph!
Wardrobe from the Jim Fowler collection.
Ralph! Quickly! Ralph!
Quick! Eastenders is on!
Move, UPS worker.
The pollen is in the...
[grunts]
It's much better in here, thank you.
She'll be all right. Get rid of those towels.
Eww.
She's just ahead now.
Her feet are still on fire.
When I wake, I'm going to be mildly interested in morphemes.
The drones keep going on and on and on about how many of them were killed.
Man, the vacation's going so well until this point.
Ah, now let's review these scenes for the test.
Why do I dream of Clamato?
Avenge me, Ralph.
A couple of no-pass trips can make this whole movie go away.
Who's afraid of Virginia Woolf? In hell!
Ah, in happier days.
Bad hands, naughty hands.
My manicure still looks great.
She saw us! Let's go!
Why are you getting stressed? There's no need for that.
She's going to surprise General Half-Track wearing nothing but a light wrap.
Ralph!
Miss Robin, she's going!
Right in the middle of Safari.
Hey, come back here!
What do you think you're doing?
You haven't filled out a comment card!
He switches to Super Femme Run.
Give me the card, please, quickly.
Do something about the house file, would you, if you get around to it? Thank you.
Ah, I'll be fine! Ouch!
I hope you unloaded the clowns first.
He's driving a Matchbox car. Look at that.
Man, I love this time of year in England. What time of year is it?
Enough room for one egg and a magazine.
Pudding fuel cars don't have very good acceleration.
They never pedal fast enough to catch up to her.
Wait! You didn't finish your continental breakfast!
Yes!
This is a movie that has everything all wrong.
Calling all clowns, calling all clowns.
Car 37, we have a mime truck in the area with a bucket of confetti to assist. Over.
The bra of Vicki Rollins is hospitalized after sustaining minor injuries in the car accident.
The bra is listed in stable condition.
Darling, the bees have been asking after you. They're in an awful state.
Don't forget my purse, my train case, my steamer trunk.
Come on, drink this, Vicki.
Come now, it's bee juice.
You're a giant bee wearing a wig, aren't you?
All right.
Doris, I've got to get out of here.
You can't leave the island. There isn't another boat until tomorrow.
But you don't have a stand.
Take down and pin.
Try and get some rest.
We're visiting that spider farm tomorrow.
I'll get these cleaned.
You've really pitted them out.
I'll be back later.
Okay, just let the management know.
I'm going now, Ralph. I'll see you at the pub later.
Yes, I will.
I'm off to become Lulu.
We've got to get some pulse cards out.
Why does he have a collection of butcher block tables in his yard?
There was a huge smoking towel.
We lost George and Linda and Bill. The carnage was terrible.
I'll have to learn to ride this someday.
The bees built on stilts must be a flood plain.
I'm terribly sorry.
Manfred, I'm sick and tired of your bees swarming on my property.
Quite unintentional. I can't see.
I'm not unintentional. I can't think what makes them do it.
Well, that's your problem.
It's very stupid of me, I know, but as I only keep bees in a small way, I'm not an expert like yourself.
You realize, of course, I have every legal right to keep them.
Ah, oh, have you?
Oh, I didn't know that.
But I'm sure that as a friend and neighbor you would never do such a thing.
By the way, how's Miss Robbins?
She's all right.
I had thought of asking her over for a cup of tea or something.
Well, you'll have to ask her some other time. She's out walking.
I'm supposed to be out walking.
Yes.
All right.
I only hope the lack of frames doesn't cause my bees to swarm again, that's all.
They better not swarm here.
Ah, well...
And do me a favor.
Kiss me.
Organize your hives, will you?
Where can I find a nail clipper?
Giddy up, giddy up, giddy up, let's go.
Hey, it's nondescript spice.
Whose woods these are?
Oh, I think I know.
Killer cookie crumbs.
Damn, it's that bee-loud glade that Yates spoke of.
The bees want to move in with a beehive hairdo.
The hairdo.
Tea is stuffed with ham.
Hey, Crow. What you doing?
Hi. Waiting.
Oh.
For?
Oh, for Mike.
I asked him where my bottle of Just For Men hair coloring was, and he left without a word.
And so I shall await his return, for I have every faith that Mike will one day come back to me and answer the question I posed so long ago.
Mike! I knew you'd come back!
Hey, guys. How you doing? You know what? I thought I'd shake things up a bit.
You know, think outside the box. Ship the hell out of our paradigms, huh?
So you dressed in a bee costume. Good for you.
Yeah, you know, just for today, I thought I'd communicate as the bees do.
Um, bees communicate through movement and odor.
Right. I'll just be using movement.
Oh, good. Thank you.
Oh, sure. Yeah? Yeah, of course.
What's he saying?
Yes, I have to agree with Milton Friedman. Economic freedom is an essential requisite for political freedom.
Did he say anything about my Just For Men?
No, I'll let you know.
Oh, Mike. Oh, my.
What? What? What? This has to be about my Just For Men hair coloring.
I'm stirring. You, my friend, are one of the few people who can do justice to Chief Seattle's oration.
Thank you, Mike. Thank you.
What about my Just For Men hair coloring?
I'm sure he's getting to that crow. Geez.
Say, Mike, can you compare and contrast the English translation and the Mahabharata to the original Sanskrit?
Ah, yes. I see. Yes, I understand. I agree. Uh-huh. Yeah.
I mean, I don't really need it.
It's just, you know, I enjoy looking younger.
Nothing wrong with that, I don't think.
Oh, anyway, we'll be right back. Yep.
Later that second, the weather cleared up.
Doris?
She's headed right for the honeycomb hideout.
Now she jumps in the water in their class four rapids.
She's headed for the water. Get your scuba gear on, man. Go on in.
Yes, sir, I did see a small paragraph in the paper a few days ago, sir, but I didn't think anything of it, sir.
Guess you're what, sir? Yes, sir?
Well, sir, I didn't think you'd wish to be bothered with any trifling coincidence like that, sir.
Is it up my what, sir? Yes, sir.
Harcourt, sir? Uh, no, sir, I'm afraid Harcourt isn't in today, sir.
Tomorrow morning, sir. Take a flying what, sir?
Yes, of course, sir.
Yes, sir. Yes, don't worry, sir. I'll have him on his way first thing in the morning.
His hair needs dusting.
I think I'll go into the other part of the room now. Yes, yes.
Bzzt! Kidding.
For your imminent murder!
Now, I'll be back before lunch and perhaps you'll feel more like eating something then.
You're not leaving me.
Well, I have to. I must get inside the Hargrove farm.
But why?
Well, we've got very nearly all the evidence we need, but there are still one or two pieces necessary to complete the jigsaw.
But why? But I got you all those papers.
Yes. The bees ate them, yes.
But there was that book that Hargrove saw you reading.
Perhaps if we could get hold of that, well, that might help us.
Can you remember the title?
Yes.
The something. Does that help?
Something by a man called Simmons. Bee farming.
Hargrove would never let you take it.
Well, we can try, can't we? And after all you've been through, well, we mustn't let you down.
He should wash his teacup.
Be careful, aren't you?
I can't be careful. I'm not made that way, baby.
I can look after myself, don't you worry. Now, you just take it easy. I'll be back before lunch and I'll get that book somehow.
If anyone comes around, just say, "But why?"
You realize, of course, that you came straight here from the nursing home.
She suffered a severe mental breakdown.
Yes, I know. Well, that may account for her behavior.
She's been diagnosed as mental.
All right, I'll get her bags. Excuse me.
I'll wait out here.
I wonder if you'd like to puncture the horse with me.
Okay, we've all got our alibis, right?
But why?
Wait, I'm reading. Get the light. Wait.
I'm going backpacking through the British Isles.
If you're looking for her panties, I'm already wearing the good ones.
Well, that's all the gear.
I'm afraid she was quite adamant about staying at my place. So what can I do?
I couldn't care less.
Oh, I see.
Hogrove, I wonder if I could borrow your copy of the Simmons book on bee farming.
I've mislaid mine and I'm a bit lost without it.
Picked up that I'm mad at you?
Yes, I've got one somewhere. There shall be minutes.
Yes, that's right. Get that book. Bend over to get it. Here.
How to raise bees to kill people?
Beekeeping for lunatics?
Apiaries for the criminally insane?
Hmm.
I must ask him, but why when he returns?
Okay, I'll lend him this, but he has to let me borrow Mandingo.
Thank you. I'm getting very untidy at the cottage these days. I can't find anything.
So there you are. One of the advantages of having your wife do look after you.
Don't.
I'm sorry. I...
Well, thank you for the book. I'll bring it over tomorrow.
Keep it.
Through the ages, people keep bees. The end.
Hmm. When have I seen this guy?
What? Why is that so shocking? What's going on?
Well, the movie's trying to shake us guys.
I guess.
And the horrible truth is revealed. He makes fake designer fragrances.
I never got to go parasailing on this vacation.
Just have to go back and get her piano and...
Hope she won't find it off-putting when I dress like my mother.
This is great. What other vacation can you pretend you work at a Pro-X lab?
Just had to adjust my trust there.
Draw.
Hello?
This is an odd version of Shadowlands.
Feeling better?
I guess.
You may be wrong, but no one seems to like me at all.
Well, I think there's room in the crawl space for one more body.
Hmm. Yes.
I've got to stop trapping my brides, you know. It's lost its appeal. There's something so coercive about it.
What do you think, bow-tie?
Well, Vicki, I'm no absolutely certain as to how Hargrove controls his being.
Blackmail.
You found it in the book?
All I needed to know.
But if the book was so important, why did he lend it?
To kill you. I mean, I'm not sure.
It required a certain amount of cunning on my part to get it.
I left him very angry, and of course I had his precious book.
Mike, you don't need to watch your shoes for a while. It makes about as much sense.
Now we can tell the police.
Feel free.
Yes. First thing in the morning.
Surely we can tell Mr. Hawkins?
No. Mr. Hawkins is too upset. Doris is still very ill.
I'll be, uh, you know where.
[Music]
I thought we'd have some tea.
But then I thought, no, I'll keep it all for myself.
Oh, and I thought I'd killed you.
So, why did this movie cost 170 million?
I don't know.
You're wondering how I stay so lumpy, aren't you?
Would you like to pour?
What you doing?
None of your beeswax.
Oh, just making a few preparations.
Which one is my hole? I forget.
The bees are getting angry.
Why?
Oh, their football team lost.
They're getting ready to swarm.
Oh, don't ask about us birds.
But obviously you know that I've been lying.
The killer bees are mine, not Hargrove's.
Well, these are their. I've got thousands and thousands of them.
How do you tell an angry bee from a placid bee anyway?
They always seem kind of irritating.
Hargrove knew as well.
He started experimenting himself.
You said I could pour.
So I fixed him.
You see, Vicki, you're coming to the Hargrove farm as a godsend in a way.
Here you are right now.
Hargrove had suspected for some time that I'd developed a new strain of bees
that I could send anywhere and attack anyone.
And he tried to find out how I did it.
So I arranged for my bees to attack him.
Fly, monkeys, fly.
I placed the liquid which attracts the bees on one of his buckets.
Unfortunately, Mrs. Hargrove got it on herself and the bees killed her.
It turns out it was devious aphids dressed up as bees.
Thanks for this again.
Mind you, everyone blamed Hargrove.
We blame you, Hargrove.
Including you.
I blame you.
But I still didn't know how close he was to my little secret.
Yes, yes.
That was why I sent you to photograph his papers.
And after that, I'm afraid, I no longer had any use for you.
I made sure that you got the smell of fear on yourself.
Rubbing it quite obviously on yourself.
You escaped.
And poor Doris, well, I hadn't intended the bees to attack her.
I'm not great at the murder thing, but I'm getting a bit better.
Fortunately, she dropped the cardigan and escaped with only a few stings.
You thought it was Hargrove who tried to kill you.
The flashback is as long as the movie should have been.
So you came to me for protection and stayed here while I went to get rid of Hargrove.
The Simmons book was just an excuse.
Well, obviously, I already had a copy, but I pretended I wanted to borrow his.
Hargrove, I wonder if I could borrow your copy of the Simmons book on bee farming.
I've mislaid mine and I'm a bit lost without it.
Man, this was three minutes ago.
Yes, I'll go once somewhere. I shall go.
I decided not to narrate this part of my flashback. I think it speaks for itself.
And while Hargrove was looking for the book.
I looked at Hargrove.
I placed the liquid which attracts the bees on his jacket.
I did a good job. I must say I was pleased with the fluid distribution.
Suddenly I forgot what I was doing.
Then I started telling you about this situation and that brings us to the next part.
You killed Hargrove?
Yes, I think he was trying to pinch my idea.
You know, Vicki, there are very few people that I dislike, but I couldn't stand Hargrove.
He was so rude.
I mean, just imagine what would have happened if my bees had got into the hands of an irresponsible villain like Hargrove.
He treated Mrs. Hargrove abominably. Don't leave me, Vicki.
I haven't finished killing you yet.
I'm talking to you.
I'm talking to you. You see, I have to kill you.
Why didn't you just say so instead of boring her?
Ah, breakfast.
Inspector Bartender at work.
Hat from the Norman Fell line.
You said you were off the junk, Nelly.
If I don't miss my guests, this is a horse of some kind.
Does that smell me or the horse?
Jerry Orbach in Hatari.
Ah, here's my gaily colored sport coat.
No, he's going to try to steal my checked hat.
I'm just going to wait for a flashback to explain all this.
Oh, man, it was a long, chilly walk from the house.
The gin well was a great idea.
I'd go a long way.
Cinematography by Angel Cordero.
Nothing. Nothing. Nothing. Nothing.
The one with the business.
I haven't picked the soup of the day.
Yep, with star power like this, how could this movie miss?
Good heavens, they're beautiful.
Hawkins, don't move.
Especially don't do the Watusi.
Hawkins, don't move. Especially don't do the Watusi.
Oops.
Hey! Stop, jacket theme, stop!
Get him out of it! Let's sting him on the lip, make him look funny.
Hawkins, stop that jacket!
Now the trousers.
Hawkins, get rid of that jacket!
It doesn't flatter you at all!
Paris tweed, it drives me crazy.
This Tommy Chong in a can will take care of it.
Hey, look, I beefed. Did you ever think such a big deal about it?
Don't you understand it was my jacket the bees were attacking and not you?
Your jacket?
Yes. Manfred was here about an hour ago.
Obviously treated my jacket in some way with something so that his bees would attack me.
His bees killed my wife and attacked your daughter.
Don't you understand? The man's a homicidal maniac!
Now first I will immobilize the bees.
Look, it's okay, just go ahead and kill me.
Stop talking.
Xeroxed her expression and taped it to her face.
I'm saving up for a better sound system.
I've made this movie really hard to watch.
Especially for you, Vicky.
It's aromatherapy.
Bested by the mother's father.
You've been putting filler in our bee, fool.
Nice bees, uh, nice bees, flippie.
Time to brand the carriage.
I'm watching you guys, it's the flaming towel lady.
Wow, she's actually caused more damage and destruction than any of the bees.
I'll pat the doorbell.
Pat, pat.
These look like flying cocktail wheels.
Oh man, you can't blame that on the bees.
Vicky must be here.
Don't push to the inside, I'm pushing from the outside.
Ow!
Now let me run around to the window and get...
The house was made of typing patron oily rags.
Poor dumb bees, assuming he's there to rescue them.
Unfortunately, she's got a timeshare on this island, so she can come back every year.
Oh great.
Goodbye, Vicky.
I suppose the pop world will seem pretty dull out to Seagull Island.
Yes, it'll seem quite restful.
Bye now.
Bye.
Just move those confetti buckets and cream pies out of the way there, ma'am.
See you, Dave.
And the bees were sentenced to life imprisonment with no chance of parole.
Happy music now, I want everything to play.
Hey, what the hell?
Nothing, though.
It's a guy from the Magritte painting.
Wait, wait a minute, what the hell?
Okay, start slooching movies. What the hell is this?
So is there a credit that says "guy at the end"?
Hello, I'm here for the movie. Am I late? Hello?
I think he's showing up for a Pink Floyd video.
What a pain in the...
Maybe there's a time when bowler-headed guys could open a movie.
So, what do you think the message of the movie was?
Don't watch it.
Never.
So, bees, huh?
Yep, they sure make a film.
Sure do. Bees should be in every single movie.
Yep.
Oh, Pearl's calling.
Well, Mike, it's Armageddon.
These other bleaching-faced, fae, omnipotent brain guys are battling our brain guy because he decided to stay.
Once they toast him, they're gonna take over the world.
An idea they totally stole from me.
You flesh-loving traitor!
I shan't!
Surrender, carnally besotted fool!
Well, meet your dude!
No, it's stereo this time, observer.
Too at once! Too much!
Can't handle it!
I need more chili dogs!
Chili dogs? What a fascinating concept!
Yes, with lots of yummy, ooey, gooey cheese!
Cheese? What an intriguing notion!
Quick, Pearl! Put this down the laundry chute!
What do I look like? Your maid?
Hurry, the fate of the world is in balance!
Hurry, the fate of the world is in...
Hurry up!
My brain!
So, it comes down to you and it comes down to me.
And me, eh, observer?
To the supreme challenge of our respective neural mastery!
Quick, Pearl, go long!
My brain! My beautiful brain!
My...
So, former brain mates!
For punishment, you shall walk this earth for the rest of your days as mere flesh-bound mortals.
Worse yet, you will live in Wisconsin, where you will work at the Burnett County Dairy Cooperative.
And be raging Packers fans!
Go Packers!
Packers, woo!
Hey, you got any more smokes, man?
You gotta quit bumming them.
Oh, that was fun! Let's do it again!
Laser Bobo, eh?
Have you gone? The world's saved and everything.
Yes, yes, yes! We three have triumphed over evil in a way that I...
Okay.
Huh.
Ahh!
[Music]
The dog's meat! Have you seen it?